New York State Board of Mediation Cases 5581
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- A 507 - A 713 (1939). (Box 4)
  - Hartnagel, Otto, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Silver Standard, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Empire Photographers, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - United Parcel Service, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Marder, Murray, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Edison Pharmacy, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 116)
- A 714 - A 889 (1940). (Box 5)
  - One West 39th St., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - J. Horn Furniture Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Landres-Goldfarb, Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Paragon Slipper Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Advance Pressure Castings, Inc. and Sterling Dye Casting Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Greenwood Cemetery, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Luxor Baths, Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Valentine and Company, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Freedman's Dept. Store, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Kirschbaum Express, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Levy, Harris, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - New York Pie Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Gerzog's Cafeteria, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Retail Merchants Associated Board of Trade, Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Consolidated Smoked Fish Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Clover Leaf Paint and Varnish Corp., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - M. Katz, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - West-English Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Gladstone, Alex, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Grand Theaters, Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Envoy System, Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Hattie Carnegie, Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Mario Gonzales, Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - M. Millman and Sons, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Stewart's Millinery, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - European Radio Company, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Bruner-Ritter Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Consolidated Film Industries, Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Knickerbocker Photographers, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Ajax Radiator Enclosure Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Green Bus Lines, Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Manhattan Pontiac Corp., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Swiss Radium and Dial Painting Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Abbott Furniture Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - A. Werman and Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Rialto Retailers, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - C and S Luncheonette, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Tabor and Weiser, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Metro Sacks Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Kingmore Holding Corp., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - May Hat Shoppe, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - International Hardware, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Royal Office Supply Corp., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Cornell Cab Corporation et al. (Group of Independent Taxi Operators), 1940 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Berger Gorin Press, Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Mills Sales Co. of New York, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Aaron Streit Matzohs Company, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Amalgamated Dwellings Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Goldfarb, T., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Barclay Drug Company, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - U.S. Studio and Mattress Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Saporta, O., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - United Cigar - Whelan Stores Corp., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Salwen and Keller, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - J. Horn Furniture Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Tremont Food Center (Spielman and Schlesinger), 1940 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Columbia Combining Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Kaplan Company, Joseph, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Beachview Body and Fender Corp., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Keystone Express Company, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Wucker Furniture Company, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Ramsey's "They Cannot Rip" Binghamton, N.Y., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Thomas Shoe Repair, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Kaufman, S. (United Retail Fish Dealers Assn.), 1940 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Scall Undergarment Company, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Seiler, Louis Daniel Jones, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Federal Silver Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Abbey Photo Corp., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Spear and Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - National Pad Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Accurate Shoe Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Comfort Sandal Mfg. Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Werman and Sons, Inc. A., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Kay Shop, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Bronx Silk and Woolen Company, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Fred's Auto Painting, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - National Independent Pharmacists Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Friedland Fixture Corporation, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Romeike, Henry Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Rubicon Operating Corporation, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Greenwelk Knitwear Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Cluett. Peabody and Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Tru Cut-Rate Drug Store, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Paramount Silk House Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - La Valle, Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Royal Glass Works Corp., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - J. Schwartz and Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Michaels, J., Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - East New York Bakers Association, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Schnier and Held, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Liggett Drug Company Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Flint and Horner, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Yaffa Bros. Inc. and Brooklyn Heights Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Majestic Paper Box Company, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Vic-Mark Corporation Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Binik and Frank, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 96)
- A 891 - A 1048 (1940). (Box 6)
  - Langa Bros., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - J.F.D. Manufacturing Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - East Side Metal Spinning Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Samuel H. Moss, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Nathan Packer, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Tee and Tee Pharmacy, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Victor Haida Displays, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Sternberger Motor Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Brooks Quality Furniture Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Real Kosher Sausage Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Aaron Pitter, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Empire City Apartment Supply Assn., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dandy Dry Goods Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Rialto Retailers, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Plymouth Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cushman Bakeries, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Fairchild Aerial Camera Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Interborough Wrecking Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - G. Sasso and Son, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Mendel Drug Store, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Castle and Son, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Wagner, Constantin (700 West 176th St.) (701 West 175th St.), 1940 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Merton Cushman Bakeries, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Pinaud, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Purepac Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Van Iderstine Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Bee Dept. Store, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Wucker Furniture Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Nadell, Mr. Max, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Sanitary Dash Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Reliable Furniture Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Paramount Arts, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Adeline Shops, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Consolidated Smoked Fish Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Patterson Silk, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Beyda and Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Harrico Drugs, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - M. Schaefer, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Lanner Bros., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Lewis Paper Box Corporation, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Southern Cube Specialty Corporation, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Lavenburg Co., Fred L., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Saporta, O., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Empire Dry Goods Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Mayer Herman Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Mayer Herman Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Balinsky, S. and Ruhalter, D., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Steiner Bros., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Bulckly Dunton Paper Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Globe Optical Co., Inc. Hollinger, Jos. And Son, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Eighteen Fiftyone Seventh Ave. Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Topping Bros., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Lentz, Harry, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Casket Manufacturers Assn., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Thrift Furniture Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Stuhmer, George F. and Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Nevins, Edward, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - York Studio, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Schanbel Stores Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Pal Products, Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Bergold, Charles, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Beachview Body and Fender Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Smiles Drug Stores, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Newberg's Apparel Shop, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Harris and Mermelstein, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - United Cigar Whelan Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Superior Window Cleaning Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Shopley's, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Ansbacher Siegle Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Practical Window Cleaning Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - National Grain Yeast Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - John R. Thompson Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Rose Range Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Lanner Bros., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Brooklyn Master Bakers Purchasing Assn., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Blue Baking Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Weissman's, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Murray's Cut-Rate Meat Market, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Savoy Decorators Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Abbey Photo Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Postman Trucking Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Chelsea Optical Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Rayburn Cafeteria, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Webster Cut-Rate Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Silsbe Realty Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Clarostat Manufacturing Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - United Cigar Whelan Stores Corp., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Roth's Good Service Laundry, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - William Goldenblum and Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Greater N.Y. Retail Furnishing and Dry Goods, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Win Winkle Shoe Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Capitol Wine and Spirits Co., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Asness Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Wal Course Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Ader, Sam, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - May Knitting Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Accurate Shoe Corporation, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Progress Shoe Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 98)
- A 1050 - A 1227 (1940). (Box 7)
  - Horowitz, D.L. Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pressler, Max, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Lustig's, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Storms, H.M. Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Windsor Theatre (Amrof Amusement Co.), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Well Bilt Table Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Gordon Bakery Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - J. Rothstein and Sons, Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Manhattan Optical Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Fairchild Sons, Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Triangle Stationery Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chadaby's Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Kannen Orthopedic Shoe Repairing Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Ellis Baking Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Helena Cut-Rate Drug Store, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Downtown Carton Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Franklin Machine Products Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Plymouth Restaurant, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Herman Cohen and Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Retail Bakery Clerks Union Local 1111, A.F. of L., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Breitkopf and Krauss, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Primrose Dept. Store, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Alpha Textile Printing Corporation, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Manhattan Novelty Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Careful Window Cleaning Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Commercial Window Cleaning Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Rosoff's Restaurant, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Jules Modern Millinery, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Chauffeur's Service Corp., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Downtown Carton Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - National Shoe Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Schechter-Viener, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Neon Bell Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Bookbinders and Rulers Association, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Constantin Wagner, Jr., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Cork-ees Slipper Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Cigar-Whelan Stores, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Spivack, Chaim, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Zweibel, M., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Gold and Seiden, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Glassman Box Corporation, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Dugan Bros. Inc., New York, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Gonzalez Company, Mario, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Mazur Bros., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Bloomingdale Bros., Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Goldfarb's, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Rothstein, J. and Sons, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Shapiro, Mr. Louis R., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Schwerner Oppenheim, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Wearwell Knitting Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Hygrade Products Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Halem, Harry and Messing, Louis, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Dorris Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Trans-Boro Management Corp., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Everlast Metal Corp., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Gonzales, Mario, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Fuel Merchants Association Inc. Coal Merchants Association Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Union Fisheries Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Blavatnick, Frank, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Henry Waterman and Bro. Corp., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Globe Trunk and Bag Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Orgler Envelope Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Gordon Dept. Stores Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Block, J.H. and Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Pack-In Carton Corporation, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Atlantic Yeast Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Schwarz Advertising Service, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - De Luxe Market, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Mme. Fischer's Beauty Salons Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Purity Bakeries Corporation, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Gimbel Brothers, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Lanner Bros., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Union Furniture Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Times Radio Stores, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Royal Office Supply Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Kelly, Henry and Sons, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Piser and Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Beyda and Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - B.F. Curry, Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Finocchio, John, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Parmet Bros. Furniture Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Downtown Carton Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Siegel, Sidney Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Crown Drug Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Kosher Provision Co's., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Silverman, I., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Sperry Gyroscope Corporation, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Kochman Bros., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Nussbaum, Herman, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Hellman Funeral Chapel, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Metro Sacks Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Bob's Millinery, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Collier Advertising Service, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - United Cigars- Whelan Stores Corp., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Werman and Sons, Inc. A., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Jurow's Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Sun Ray Yarn Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Sosnow, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Starkman's Fish Market, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Globe Optical Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Downtown Dry Goods Jobbers Assn., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - United Parcek Service, Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Northwestern Fruit and Produce Co., Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - London Specialty Shop, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Morris Leinwand and Co., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Breakstone Bros., Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 106)
- A 1227A - A 1421 (1941). (Box 8)
  - Greenstein, Jack, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Prompt Paper Box Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - J. Joseph's Sons Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Lippert Bros., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Miller and Van Winkle Spring Company, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Bebry Bedding Corporation, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Picadilly Pharmacy, Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ever-Ready Window Cleaning Company, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Harlem Sugar Company, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - New York Wholesale Grocery Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - City Provision Company, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Eagle Plastics Company, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Purity Bakeries Corporation, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Rubicon Operating Corporation, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Valley Stream Park Inn, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Champion Envelope Mfg. Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Gettleman Pharmacy, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Goodwin, E.H. Motor Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Centre Department Store, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Polly Prim Stores, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Paramount Silk House, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Roosevelt Art Shop, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Jackson Shade and Glass Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Johnson Fish Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Saltser and Weinsier, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Rosenwasser and Mittman, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Hertz Shoe Clinic, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Eleven Moore Street Corp., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Glassman Box Corp., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Smilen Brothers, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Atlantic Baking Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Dubrow's Cafeteria, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Rosedale Engineering Corp., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Long Island Lighting Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - National Bedding and Upholstery Manufacturers. Trade Board Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Premier Company, Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Calvert Distillers Corp., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Franklin Machine Products Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Beyda and Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Kaufman Pure Food Products, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Senter Bros., Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Neo Gravure Printing Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - White Star Market - et al., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Curry, B.F. Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Roger Smith Hotel, White Plains, N.Y., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Volk, Albert A. Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Broadyke Market, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Victor Auto Service, Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Rothman's Pharmacy, Abraham, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Caiazzo, Michael, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - H. Chagrin, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Chas. Nolte, Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Rubin, Sam, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Weintraub, Morris, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Frank J. Quigan Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Kram, Harry, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Richter Trucking Company, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Amalgamated Housing Corporation, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Fisher, Abraham I., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Dumont Electric Company, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Nathan Grobifker, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - R.K. Pastry Bakery, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - G. and G. Wholesale Bakery, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - New Deal Pharmacy, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Schlossman's, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Abe Gordon, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Paper Box Credit Bureau, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - M. Radeschi, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Gettleman Pharmacy, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Dandy Window Cleaning Company, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Tabor and Weiser, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Century Office and Building Cleaning Co. Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Bedford Parlor Framr Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Shapiro, Abraham, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Towers Shoe Company, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Arnel Company, Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Bryant Pharmacy, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Haber Crushed Fruit Corp., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Sweet., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Morgenstern, Hyman, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Trubia Bakery, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Mrs. Pikoff, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Federal Composition and Paint Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Lyonds Drugs Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Gottlieb, Harry, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - H.E.R. Laboratories, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Schindel Chain Stores, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Casket Makers, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Purveyors' Refrigerators Delivery Corp., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Nash Motors Co. of New York, Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Atlantic Baking Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Beigl, Geo. Millinery, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - City Provision Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Arco Metalcraft, Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Mazur Bros., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Mazur and Levy, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Comfort Sandal Manufacturing Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Radio Picture Frame Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Superb Glove Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Selma's Millinery, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Aiken Demolition Co., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Kannen Orthopedic Shoe Repair Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Hugo Brand Tannery, Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Screen Process and Display Assn., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Bagel Bakers Assn. of Greater N.Y., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 105)
- A 1423 - A 1623 (1941). (Box 9)
  - Lewis Steel Products, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - United Cigar - Whelan Stores Corp., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Pinaud's Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Weiner, Irving, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Meyer, Frank C. Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Teddy's Auto Radiator Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Manhattan Pontiac Corporation, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Hornick, Louis and Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Famous Myrtle, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Siegel, Sidney, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Bellows and Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Fleishman and Steir, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Picker Drug Store, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Sandler, Sam, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Greenstein, Benjamin, Katz, Sam, Feinberg, Israel, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Smoleroff Realty Management Corp., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sweet Life Corporation, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Webster Cut-Rate Drug Store, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Fisher, Abraham I., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Landres-Goldfarb, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Goldslaug, Nathan, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Barr Wrecking Corp., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Gellis, Isaac, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Barry, E.J., Drug Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - French Powder Puff Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Fada Radio and Electric Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Guilford Farms, The, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Vicmark Corporation, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Frucht, Joseph, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Klappholtz-Schornstein Baking Corp., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Main Street Bakery, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Colonial Body Corp., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Carmel Kosher Provision Co., Inc. and Hebrew National Kosher Sausage Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Oxenberg Bros., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Melo Envelope and Paper Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - City Service Window Cleaning Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Gimbel Brothers, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Elm Pharmacy, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Royal Felt and Batting Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 39)